Guide to the Jack Gelber Papers 1938-2002 (Bulk 1957-1999) MSS.146
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Production Files
  - Subseries A: The Connection
    - Clippings and Advertisements, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 898)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIA Oversize, Box 48, Folder 1202
    - Clippings, Advertisements, and Programs, 1963-1997, Undated (Box 17, Folder 899)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIA Oversize, Map Case, Drawer 3G, Folder 1203
    - Clippings, Advertisements, Programs, and Press Releases, Undated (Box 17, Folder 900)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIA Oversize, Box 48, Folder 1204
    - The Connection (Annotated Paperback) and Ticket Stubs, 1959-1960, Undated (Box 17, Folder 901)
      The Connection by Jack Gelber, New York: Grove Press, Inc., 1957, 1960
    - The Connection (Annotated Paperback), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 902)
    - Scrapbooks, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 903)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIA Oversize, Box 49
    - "The Connection Cast" (Photograph), Undated (Box 17, Folder 904)
  - Subseries B: The Apple
    - "The Apple: A Play in Three Acts" (Annotated Typescript) and Notes, 1960 (March) (Box 18, Folder 905)
    - "The Apple," Grove Press Proofing Copy (Annotated Typescript), 1961 (Box 18, Folder 906)
    - "'The Apple' Copy No. 1" (Annotated Typescript), 1960 (Box 18, Folder 907)
      The script is marked "The Living Theatre"
    - "'La Manzana,' por Jack Gelber," Unknown Translator (Typescript), 1967 (Box 18, Folder 908)
      This folder also holds a business card inscribed "Elizabeth Howell Buckley" and an envelope with the return address marked "JEM"
    - "Original 'Apple' Manuscript" (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 18, Folder 909)
    - "'The Apple,' Some New York Reviews", 1962 (Box 18, Folder 910)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIB Oversize, Box 50, Folder 1205
    - Clippings and Book Cover, 1960-1962, Undated (Box 18, Folder 911)
    - Clippings and Living Theatre Programs, 1961 (Box 18, Folder 912)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIB Oversize, Box 50, Folder 1206
    - Clippings and Programs, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 913)
    - Clippings and Advertisements, 1964, Undated (Box 18, Folder 914)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIB Oversize, Box 50, Folder 1207
  - Subseries C: On Ice
    - "Untitled Novel Volume 1" (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 19, Folder 915)
    - "Untitled Novel Volume 2" (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 19, Folder 916)
    - On Ice, Pages 1-185 (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 19, Folder 917)
    - On Ice, Pages 186-349 (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 19, Folder 918)
    - Notes, Undated (Box 19, Folder 919)
    - Portion of Esquire (July 1963) (Box 19, Folder 920)
    - Clippings and Advertisements, 1964, Undated (Box 19, Folder 921)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIC Oversize, Box 50, Folder 1208
    - "On Ice" Screenplay Adaptation (Typescript), Undated (Box 19, Folder 922)
  - Subseries D: Square in the Eye
    - Notebook, Undated (Box 19, Folder 923)
    - Notebook and Loose Notes, 1965, Undated (Box 20, Folder 924)
    - Contact Sheet, Pages from "Let's Face It" (Annotated Typescript), and Notes, 1964-1965, Undated (Box 20, Folder 925)
    - "Let's Face It: A Play in Two Acts" (Typescript), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 926)
      The script is marked "The Establishment Theatre Company"
    - "Lets Face It: A Play in Two Acts, First Draft" (Two Bound Typescripts), 1964 (Box 20, Folder 927)
    - "Let's Face It" (Bound Annotated Typescript) and Notes, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 928)
    - Notes and Pages from "Let's Face It, or Cut the Crap Charlie," "Cuba Si," and "Notes Toward a New Yorker Autobiography" (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 20, Folder 929)
      The folder that contained these items prior to processing is labeled "Original Typescripts of 'Let's Face It' and Abandoned Cuba Play"
    - "Let's Face It" (Three Annotated Typescripts) and Notes, 1963-1964, Undated (Box 20, Folder 930)
    - "Let's Face It: A Play in Two Acts" (Typescript), Undated (Box 20, Folder 931)
    - "'Let's Face It:' Estimated Weekly Operating Expenses", Undated (Box 21, Folder 932)
    - Clippings and Theatre De Lys Program, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 933)
  - Subseries E: The Cuban Thing
    - Festival de Teatro Latinoamericano: Clippings, Journal Entries, Flyers, and Notes, 1964, Undated (Box 21, Folder 934)
    - "Cuban Visit by Jack Gelber" (Two Typescripts), Undated (Box 21, Folder 935)
    - "Cuba Si!" Materials, 1963-1965, Undated (Box 21, Folder 936)
      The contents of this folder include notes, bibliographies, portions of an untitled script, and a booklet: "Cuban Assets Control: Regulations and Related Documents," The Treasury Department, July 8, 1963
    - "The Cuban Thing: A Play in Two Acts" (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 21, Folder 937)
    - Untitled Script and "Cuba, Si" (Incomplete Typescripts), Undated (Box 21, Folder 938)
    - "The Cuban Thing" (Annotated Typescript) and Notes, 1968, Undated (Box 21, Folder 939)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIE Oversize, Box 50, Folder 1209
    - "Cuba Si" (Annotated Typescripts) and Notes, Undated (Box 22, Folder 940)
      The contents of this folder appear to be multiple incomplete versions of the script, the largest of which is 28 pages in length
    - "The Cuban Thing, First Draft" (Typescript), 1968 (Box 22, Folder 941)
      The contents of this folder also include a business card inscribed "London International, Park House" and the script is marked "Property of Ivor David Balding and Associates, The New Theatre"
    - "The Cuban Thing, First Draft" (Bound Typescript), 1968 (Box 22, Folder 942)
      The script is marked "Property of Ivor David Balding and Associates, The New Theatre"
    - "The Cuban Thing, First Draft" (Bound Typescript), 1968 (Box 22, Folder 943)
    - "The Cuban Thing" (Bound Typescript), 1968 (Box 22, Folder 944)
    - Clippings and Notes, 1967-1968, Undated (Box 22, Folder 945)
      Some of the notes were written on reverse of an undated memo from "I.D.B." [Ivor David Balding?]
    - Clippings, 1968 (Box 22, Folder 946)
    - Het Zoldertheatre Scrapbook, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 947)
      The scrapbook's contents include correspondence from Ron, [Maijolyn] Mink, and Han Mink as well as programs, clippings, advertisements and photographs
  - Subseries F: Sleep
    - "Sleep: A Play" (Typescript), 1970 (Box 23, Folder 948)
    - "'Sleep' Second Version" (Typescript), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 949)
    - "Sleep" (Annotated Typescript), Contact Sheet, and Rehearsal Schedule for American Place Theatre, 1972, Undated (Box 23, Folder 950)
      The script is marked "The American Place Theatre"
    - "Sleep" (Typescript), Undated (Box 23, Folder 951)
    - "Sleep" Materials, 1968-1969, Undated (Box 23, Folder 952)
      This folder's contents include a letter from Bernard Beckerman written on the reverse of a typescript titled "Amusing Anecdote Number 1, Life Lessons" and annotated drafts of "Sleep" along with short stories, original sketches, and notes.
    - "Sleep" (Typescript), 1997 (Box 23, Folder 953)
    - Clippings, Advertisements, Programs, and a Sketch, 1972, Undated (Box 23, Folder 954)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIF Oversize, Box 50, Folder 1210
    - La Ma Ma, e.t.c. Clippings and Advertisements, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 955)
  - Subseries G: Barbary Shore
    - 'Norman Mailer's Barbary Shore' Adapted by Jack Gelber (Annotated Typescript), 1973 (Box 24, Folder 956)
      The script is marked "Property of the New York Shakespeare Festival"
    - "Norman Mailer's Barbary Shore" (Annotated Typescript) New York Shakespeare Festival, Annotated Audition Form, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 957)
    - Casting Materials, Advertisements, and Annotated Portions of "Norman Mailer's Barbary Shore" (Typescript), 1973, Undated (Box 24, Folder 958)
    - First Page of "A Hungry Mental Lion" by Seymour Krim (Photocopy), Undated (Box 24, Folder 959)
    - New York Shakespeare Festival: 'Barbary Shore' Contact Sheet", 1973 (Box 24, Folder 960)
    - Clippings and Advertisements, 1974, Undated (Box 24, Folder 961)
  - Subseries H: Rehearsal
    - "Rehearsal" Reviews, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 962)
    - "Jack Gelber's New Play: Rehearsal" (Annotated Photocopy), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 963)
    - "Jack Gelber's New Play: Rehearsal" (Typescript), 1977 (Box 24, Folder 964)
    - "Jack Gelber's New Play: Rehearsal" (Typescript), 1976 (Box 24, Folder 965)
      This script's original containing folder is marked "International Creative Management" and the script itself is marked "The American Place Theatre"
    - "Jack Gelber's New Play: Rehearsal" (Annotated Typescript) and Notes, Undated (Box 24, Folder 966)
    - "'Eat Shit' Early Versions" and Untitled Manuscript (Annotated Typescripts), Undated (Box 25, Folder 967)
    - "Jack Gelber's New Play: Rehearsal" (Typescript), 1976 (Box 25, Folder 968)
      The original containing folder is marked "International Creative Management" and the script is labeled "Presented by Audrey Wood"
    - "Jack Gelber's New Play" (Bound Typescript), Undated (Box 25, Folder 969)
    - "Jack Gelber's New Play: Rehearsal" (Bound Typescript), Undated (Box 25, Folder 970)
      This script is marked "The American Place Theatre"
    - "New Play" (Typescript), 1974 (Box 25, Folder 971)
    - "Jack Gelber's New Play: Rehearsal" (Typescript), Undated (Box 25, Folder 972)
    - "Jack Gelber's New Play: Rehearsal" (Two Typescripts), Undated (Box 25, Folder 973)
      The scripts are marked "The American Place Theatre"
    - "Eat Shit" (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 26, Folder 974)
    - American Place Theatre Clippings, Advertisements, and Program, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 975)
  - Subseries I: Starters
    - "Starters" (Bound Typescript), 1984 (Box 26, Folder 976)
    - "Starters" (Bound Typescript), 1982 (Box 26, Folder 977)
    - "Starters, Without O'Neill" (Bound Typescript), 1980 (Box 26, Folder 978)
    - "Starters" (Bound Typescript), 1981 (Box 26, Folder 979)
    - "Starters, Version A" (Typescript), 1980 (January) (Box 26, Folder 980)
    - Clippings, Advertisements, and Production Materials, 1979-1982, Undated (Box 26, Folder 981)
    - "'Starters' Second Version With Revisions" (Typescript), 1981 (June) (Box 27, Folder 982)
    - "Starters" (Annotated Typescript) and Notes, 1981 (May), Undated (Box 27, Folder 983)
      The notes are written on the reverse side of a message from Brooklyn College (City University of New York)
    - "Starters" (Bound Typescript), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 984)
    - "Starters" (Bound Annotated Typescript) and Notes, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 985)
      The notes are written on the reverse of a letter from Washington University in St. Louis
    - "Starters" (Annotated Typescript), Notes, and Eugene O'Neill Theatre Center: 1981 National Playwrights Conference Programs, 1981-1984, Undated (Box 27, Folder 986)
    - "Starters" (Typescript), with Inserts, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 987)
    - "Starters" (Typescript), 1984 (Box 27, Folder 988)
    - "Starters" (Annotated Typescript) and Notes, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 989)
      Some of the Notes in this folder were written on a torn letter from New York University
    - "Starters" (Annotated Photocopy and Typescript) and Notes, 1982-1983, Undated (Box 28, Folder 990)
    - "Starters" (Two Bound Typescripts) and Notes, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 991)
      The first typescript bears annotations
    - "Starters, Tues 4/6/82 Latest Revision" (Annotated Typescript) and Notes, 1982 (April) (Box 28, Folder 992)
      The first page of Notes is written on the reverse of a letter from the Philadelphia Festival Theatre for New Plays, the second was written on an unsigned letter, and the last on the reverse of a "'Starters' Rehearsal Schedule"
    - "Starters" (Annotated Typescript), 1981-1982 (Box 28, Folder 993)
    - "Starters" (Typescript), Undated (Box 28, Folder 994)
    - "'Starters,' Third Version with O'Neill Corrections" (Typescript with Inserts)), 1980 (Box 28, Folder 995)
    - "Starters,' Second Version" (Typescript), 1980 (Box 29, Folder 996)
    - "Starters,' First Version" (Bound Typescript), Undated (Box 29, Folder 997)
    - "Starters" Complete Version (Annotated Typescript), 1979 (Box 29, Folder 998)
    - Sections from Multiple Versions of " Starters" (Annotated Typescript), 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 999)
    - Notes, an Untitled Annotated Typescript, "Yellow Bellied Sapsucker, 1st Version" (Annotated Typescript), and Sections from Multiple Versions of "Starters" (Annotated Typescript), 1974?-1979 (Box 29, Folder 1000)
    - Philadelphia Festival Theatre for New Plays: Flyers, Program, and a Review, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 1001)
  - Subseries J: Big Shot
    - "Big Shot Contract" (Handwritten Notes), Undated (Box 29, Folder 1002)
    - East Coast Arts at Wildcliff, Program, Undated (Box 29, Folder 1003)
    - "'Talking to the Walls' First Draft" (Annotated Typescript), 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1004)
    - "'Talking to the Walls' First Draft, Second Printing" (Annotated), 1986 (Box 29, Folder 1005)
    - Production Materials, Notes, and Pages from "Big Shot" (Annotated Typescript), 1988, Undated (Box 30, Folder 1006)
    - "Gibby" Typescripts and Notes, 1986, Undated (Box 30, Folder 1007)
    - "Gibby, Current Casting", 1988, Undated (Box 30, Folder 1008)
      The contents of this folder include casting materials, notes, a contact sheet, a rehearsal/performance schedule, and set design sketches; Some of the notes were written on the reverse sides of a letter from East Cost Arts and a memo from Brooklyn College (City University of New York); For Oversize See: Series IIJ Oversize, Box 50, Folder 1211
    - "'Big Shot' Casting", 1988, Undated (Box 30, Folder 1009)
    - "Big Shot" Materials, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 1010)
      The contents of this folder include photocopies from A Yiddish Word Book for English Speaking People and the Yiddish Dictionary Sourcebook along with annotated typescript pages from "Big Shot" (possibly multiple versions thereof), a "Scene Breakdown," and a "Rehearsal Schedule" for East Coast Arts and Writer's Theatre
    - "Big Shot" (Annotated Typescript), "Cast Contact Sheet," and Notes, 1986, Undated (Box 30, Folder 1011)
    - "Revised 'Big Shot'" (Typescript), 1989 (Box 30, Folder 1012)
    - "'Big Shot,' Circle Rep Reading" (Annotated Typescript), 1989 (October) (Box 30, Folder 1013)
    - "Big Shot" (Bound Typescript), 1989 (Box 31, Folder 1014)
    - "Big Shot" (Bound Typescript), 1988 (Box 31, Folder 1015)
    - "Big Shot" (Bound Annotated Typescript), 1988 (Box 31, Folder 1016)
    - "Big Shot" (Bound Typescript), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1017)
    - "Big Shot" (Bound Typescript), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1018)
      The script is marked "Represented by Peregrine Whittlesey"
    - "Big Shot" (Bound Annotated Typescript), 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1019)
    - East Coast Arts: Clipping, Advertisement, and Program, 1988, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1020)
  - Subseries K: Magic Valley
    - "Magic Valley" (Two Typescripts), Notes, BAT Theatre Advertisement, and Casting Materials, 1991-1999, Undated (Box 31, Folder 1021)
      The second typescript is marked "5/1/99 Corrections"
    - Large Notebook and Loose Notes, 1981, Undated (Box 32, Folder 1022)
      The notebook's contents include a draft of and notes regarding "Magic Valley" and a variety of other topics. It also holds original drawings and set design sketches for an unidentified play as well as notes regarding "The Connection," contact information for a number of individuals (including several directors, actors, and producers), and concepts for untitled plays.
    - "Magic Valley" (Typescript), 1999 (Box 32, Folder 1023)
    - Clippings and Advertisements, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 1024)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIK, Box 50, Folder 1212
  - Subseries L: Chambers
    - "'Chambers' Casting", 1997, Undated (Box 32, Folder 1025)
      This folder's contents include notes, schedules, actor's resumes, and portions of the "Chambers" script (dated October 1997)
    - "Chambers" Materials, 1995-1997, Undated (Box 32, Folder 1026)
      The contents of this folder include notes, articles regarding Alger Hiss and Whittaker Chambers, outlines, and an annotated 1995 Typescript version of "Chambers"
    - Research Material and Notes, 1994-1997, Undated (Box 32, Folder 1027)
      For Oversize Materials See: Series IIL Oversize, Box 50, Folder 1213
    - "'Chambers' Revised" (Two Typescripts), 1997 (December) (Box 33, Folder 1028)
    - "Chambers" (Two Typescripts), 1997 (November) (Box 33, Folder 1029)
    - "Chambers" (Annotated Typescript), 1997 (April-November) (Box 33, Folder 1030)
    - "'Chambers' Revised" (Two Typescripts), 1997 (April) (Box 33, Folder 1031)
      The contents of this folder include an annotated copy of a letter from [Jack Gelber] to "Arthur" dated April 3, 1997
    - "A Chambers Play" (Annotated and Regular Typescript), 1996 (December) (Box 33, Folder 1032)
      The contents of folders 1032 and1033 were originally held together in one folder
    - "A Chambers Play" (Typescript), 1996 (December) (Box 33, Folder 1033)
    - "A Chambers Play" (Annotated Typescript), Notes, and Casting Material, 1995 (December)-1996 (January), Undated (Box 34, Folder 1034)
    - "A Chambers Play" (Annotated Typescript), 1996 (December) (Box 34, Folder 1035)
    - "A Chambers Play" (Typescript), 1996 (February) (Box 34, Folder 1036)
      The contents of 1036 and 1037 were originally in one folder
    - "A Chambers Play" (Typescript), 1996 (February) (Box 34, Folder 1037)
    - November 22, 1999 Issue of The Nation (Box 34, Folder 1038)
      This item includes the book review "A Son's Own Story [Review of A View From Alger's Window by Anthony Hiss]" by Jack Gelber, The Nation Volume 269 Number 17 (November 22, 1999), New York: The Nation Company, L.P., 1999
    - Actor's Studio Free Theatre: Advertisement and Program, Undated (Box 34, Folder 1039)
      The second program is annotated
    - "Chambers" Screenplay (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 34, Folder 1040)
  - Subseries M: Rio Preserved
    - "Rio Preserved" (Two Typescripts) and Notes, 1984, Undated (Box 34, Folder 1041)
      The second typescript bears some annotations
    - "Rio Preserved" (Bound Typescript), 1984 (November) (Box 35, Folder 1042)
    - "Rio Preserved" (Bound Typescript), 1984 (Box 35, Folder 1043)
    - "Rio Preserved" (Typescript), "Third World Gods, or Invasion" (Annotated Typescript), and Notes, Undated (Box 35, Folder 1044)
    - "Rio, Various Drafts, Brazil", Undated (Box 35, Folder 1045)
      The contents of this folder include "Third World Gods" (Annotated Typescript) and an excerpt from The Cruel Dilemmas of Development by Sylvia A. Hewlett, New York: Basic Books, 1980 (Photocopy)
    - "Rio Preserved" (Typescript), Undated (Box 35, Folder 1046)
    - "Rio Preserved" (Annotated Typescript) and Notes, 1993, Undated (Box 35, Folder 1047)
    - "Rio Preserved" (Typescript), 2000 (Box 35, Folder 1048)
    - "Rio Preserved" (Annotated Typescripts), 2001, Undated (Box 35, Folder 1049)
  - Subseries N: Dylan's Line
    - "Dylan's Line" (Typescript), 2002 (Box 36, Folder 1050)
    - "Tough Love" (Annotated Typescript), 2001 (Box 36, Folder 1051)
    - "Dylan's Line" (Typescript), 2000 (Box 36, Folder 1052)
  - Subseries O: The Last Ten Minutes
    - Draft Versions Three Through Six of "The Last Ten Minutes" (Typescripts) and Notes, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 1053)
      Drafts Three, Four and Five are annotated. The notes are written on the reverse of an undated letter from Patrick Vaughn.
    - "The Last Ten Minutes" Draft Version Six, Undated (Box 36, Folder 1054)
  - Subseries P: Plays Directed
    - "The Kitchen" (by Arnold Wesker) Production Notes and Clippings, 1966, Undated (Box 36, Folder 1055)
    - "Indians" by Arthur Kopit, (Bound Annotated Typescript), 1968 (Box 36, Folder 1056)
    - "Indians" Royal Shakespeare Theatre Estimate of Production Costs, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 1057)
    - "Indians," Aldwych Theatre Program, Undated (Box 36, Folder 1058)
    - "Indians," Playbill Program, 1968 (Box 36, Folder 1059)
    - "Indians" Production Materials, Undated (Box 36, Folder 1060)
      The contents of this folder include annotated portions of the script, cast and prop lists, clippings, and notes; For Oversize Material See: Series IIP Oversize, Map Case, Drawer 3G, Folder 1214
    - "Indians" Clippings, 1962-1968 (Box 36, Folder 1061)
    - "Plays" by Jack Temchin (Bound Typescript), 1970 (Box 37, Folder 1062)
    - "Kool Aid" (by Merle Merlofsky) Advertisement and Annotated Contact Sheet, Undated (Box 37, Folder 1063)
    - "Kool Aid: Grail Green" by Merle Merlofsky, (Bound Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 37, Folder 1064)
    - "Kool Aid: Three Street Koans" by Merle Merlofsky, (Bound Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 37, Folder 1065)
    - "The Chickencoop Chinaman," (by Frank Chin) Review, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 1066)
    - "The Kid" (by Robert Coover) Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 1067)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIP Oversize, Box 50, Folder 1215
    - "Hamlet" (by William Shakespeare), Circle in the Square Theater Workshop Advertisement, Undated (Box 37, Folder 1068)
    - "A Streetcar Named Desire" (by Tennessee Williams) Academy Festival Theatre Advertisements and Stagebill Program, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 1069)
    - "A Streetcar Named Desire," Production Materials, Undated (Box 37, Folder 1070)
    - "Eulogy for a Small Time Thief" by Miguel Pinero (Typescript), Undated (Box 37, Folder 1071)
    - "Eulogy for a Small Time Thief," Annotated Pages of the Script (Photocopies), Undated (Box 37, Folder 1072)
    - "Eulogy for a Small Time Thief" Ensemble Studio Theatre Program, Undated (Box 37, Folder 1073)
    - "Seduced" by Sam Shepard, Two Photocopies of Annotated Scripts for Act 1 with an Annotated Typescript for Act 2, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 1074)
      This folder holds multiple versions of pages 1-57
    - "Seduced" by Sam Shepard, Acts One and Two, (Annotated Typescript), 1978 (Box 37, Folder 1075)
      This folder holds pages 1-61; For Oversize Material See: Series IIP Oversize, Box 50, Folder 1216
    - "Seduced by Seduced" by Jack Gelber, (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 37, Folder 1076)
    - "Seduced" (by Sam Shepard) Clippings and Advertisements, 1979, Undated (Box 37, Folder 1077)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIP Oversize, Box 50, Folder 1217
    - "The Man and the Fly" (by Jose Ruibal) Production Notes and Teatro Rodante Puertorriqueno Flyer (Annotated), Undated (Box 38, Folder 1078)
    - "El Hombre y la Mosca" by Jose Ruibal, (Annotated Photocopy), Undated (Box 38, Folder 1079)
      The script is marked "Script III," it is a photocopy of El Hombre y la Mosca, by Jose Ruibal, [Madrid: Editorial Fundamentos, 1977]
    - "The Man and the Fly" by Jose Ruibal, (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 38, Folder 1080)
    - "Questions for the Maria Guerrero Theatre" (Annotated Typescript), Undated (Box 38, Folder 1081)
    - "The Man and the Fly" (by Jose Ruibal) Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre Program and Reviews, 1982-1983 (Box 38, Folder 1082)
      For Oversize Material See: Series IIP Oversize, Box 50, Folder 1218
    - "The Dolphin Position" (by Percy Granger): Ensemble Studio Theatre Program, Review, and Flyer, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 1083)
    - "The House of Ramon Iglesia" (by Jose Rivera) Scrapbook, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 1084)
      The scrapbook includes correspondence from "Ginny" and other members of the production
    - "The House of Ramon Iglesia" Ensemble Studio Theatre Program, Reviews, and Flyer, 1983, Undated (Box 38, Folder 1085)
    - "Night Music" by Clifford Odets, Script (Annotated Photocopy), and Production Materials, Undated (Box 38, Folder 1086)